소녀시대
THE BOYS (English Ver.)
I can tell you’re lookin at me
네가 날 보고있다고 말할 수있어
I know what you see
나는 네가 뭘 보는지 알지
Any closer and you’ll feel the heat
가까울수록 열기를 느낄 수 있지
G.G
지.지
You don't have to pretend that you didn't notice me
너는 나를 못 알아본 척 할 필요 없어
Every look will make it hard to breathe
볼 때마다 숨이 막히게 될거야
T.R.X
티.알.엑스
Bring the boys out
남자애들 데리고 나와
(Yeah You know)
(그래 알겠지)
B-Bring the boys out
남자애들 데리고 나와
(We bring the boys out)
(우리가 남자애들 나오게 할거야)
(We bring the boys out yeah~)
(우리가 남자애들 나오게 할거야 예~)
B-Bring the boys out
남자애들 데리고 나와
Soon as I step on the scene
내가 여기에 발을 들여놓은 순간
I know that they’ll be watching me
그들이 날 쳐다볼거란 걸 알아
Watching me
날 쳐다볼거야
(Get up)
일어나
I’ma be the hottest in this spot
내가 여기서 가장 핫 할거야
There ain’t no stopping me (That’s funny)
날 막을 것은 없어 (웃기네)
Stopping me
날 막으려하다니
I know life is a mystery
인생은 미스테리라는 걸 알아
I’m gonna make history
나는 역사를 만들어 나갈거야
I’m taking it from the start
처음부터 새로 시작할거야
Call all emergency
모두에게 비상전화를 걸어
I’m watching the phone ring
난 전화기가 울리는 걸 지켜볼게
I’m feeling this in my heart
나의 마음 속에서 느껴져
(My heart)
(나의 마음에서)
B-Bring the boys out
남자애들 데리고 나와
Girls’ Generation make you feel the heat
소녀시대가 열기를 느끼게 만들어줄게
And we’re doin it we can’t be beat
우리가 하겠어. 우린 좀 최고거든
(B-Bring the boys out)
(남자애들 데리고 나와)
We’re born to win
우리는 승리를 하려고 태어났어
Better tell all your friends
네 모든 친구들한테 말하는게 좋을거야
Cuz we get it in
왜냐하면 우리가 여기있으니까
You know the girls
너는 소녀들을 알고있니
(Bring the boys out)
(남자애들 데리고 나와)
Wanna know my secrets
나의 비밀을 알고 싶니
But no I’ll never tell
하지만 난 절대 말 안할거야
Cuz I got the magic touch
왜냐하면 난 마법의 힘을 갖고있어서
And I’m not trying to fail
나는 실패는 하지않아
That’s right (Yes fly high!)
맞았어 (그래 높게 날아)
And I (I) (You fly high!)
그리고 나는 (나는) (너도 높게 날아)
Can’t deny
부정할 수 없어
I know I can fly
나는 날 수 있다는 걸 알고있어
I know life is a mystery
인생은 미스테리라는 걸 알아
I’m gonna make history
나는 역사를 만들어 나갈거야
I’m taking it from the start
처음부터 새로 시작할거야
Call all emergency
모두에게 비상전화를 걸어
I’m watching the phone ring
난 전화기가 울리는 걸 지켜볼게
I’m feeling this in my heart
나의 마음 속에서 느껴져
(My heart)
(나의 마음에서)
B-Bring the boys out
남자애들 데리고 나와
Girls’ Generation make you feel the heat
소녀시대가 열기를 느끼게 만들어줄게
And we’re doin it we can’t be beat
우리가 하겠어. 우리는 좀 최고거든
(B-Bring the boys out)
(남자애들 데리고 나와)
We’re born to win
우리는 승리를 하려고 태어났어
Better tell all your friends
네 모든 친구들한테 말하는게 좋을거야
Cuz we get it in
왜냐하면 우리가 여기있으니까
You know the girls
너는 소녀들을 알고있니
(B-Bring the boys out)
(남자애들 데리고 나와)
Girls bring the boys out!
소녀들이여 남자애들 데리고 나와!
I wanna dance right now
지금 당장 춤추고 싶어
We can show em how the girls get down
우리가 그들이 소녀들에게 어떻게 무릎 꿇는지 보여줄게
Yes we go for more than zero
그래 우린 최고를 뛰어넘었어
Number one everyone should know
넘버원인 걸 모두가 알아야해
Check this out
체크 디스 아웃
All’a(All the) Boys,
모든 남자애들이
All’a (All the) Boys want my heart
모든 남자애들이 내 마음을 원해
Better know how to rock and don’t stop
좀 더 어떻게 나를 흔드는지 알아내고 멈추지마
Oh gee we make it so hot
오 이런 우리가 매우 핫하게 만들어 놨어
Girls generation we won’t stop
소녀시대, 우리는 멈추지 않을거야
B-Bring the boys out
남자애들 데리고 나와
It’s not a fantasy
이게 환상은 아니야
This is right for me
이것이 나에게 맞는거지
Living it like a star
스타처럼 사는 것이 말이야
Can’t get the best of me
나를 이길 수는 없을거야
I’ma be what I wanna be
나는 내가 원하는 대로 될거야
This is deep in my heart
이것이 나의 진심이야
(My heart)
(나의 마음에서)
I can tell you’re lookin at me
네가 날 보고있다고 말할 수있어
I know what you see
나는 네가 뭘 보는지 알지
Any closer and you’ll feel the heat
가까울수록 열기를 느낄 수 있지
(Just Bring the boys out)
(바로 지금 남자애들 데리고 나와)
You don't have to pretend that you didn't notice me
너는 나를 못알아본 척 할 필요없어
Every look will make it hard to breathe
볼 때마다 숨이 막히게 될거야
(Bring the boys out)
(남자애들 데리고 나와)
Cuz the girls bring the boys out
왜냐면 소녀들이 남자애들을 데리고 나올거야
Girls bring the boys out
소녀들이여 남자애들 데리고 나와
Girls’ Generation make em feel the heat
소녀시대가 열기를 느끼게 만들어줄게
And we’re doin it we can’t be beat
우리가 하겠어. 우리는 좀 최고거든
(B-Bring the boys out)
(남자애들 데리고 나와)
We’re born to win
우리는 승리를 하려고 태어났어
Better tell all your friends
네 모든 친구들한테 말하는게 좋을거야
Cuz we get it in
왜냐하면 우리가 여기있으니까
You know the girls
너는 소녀들을 알고있니
(B-Bring the boys out)
(남자애들 데리고 나와)